Human traffickers beware.
A Working Man is a action, crime, thriller film directed by David Ayer.
Levon Cade left behind a decorated military career in the black
ops to live a simple life working construction.
But when his boss's daughter, who is like family to him, is taken by human traffickers, his search to
bring her home uncovers a world of corruption far greater than he ever could have imagined.
Levon Cade, played by Jason Statham.
Wolo Kolisnyk, played by Jason Flemyng.
Yuri, played by Merab Ninidze.
Dimi Kolisnyk, played by Maximilian Osinski.
Dougie, played by Cokey Falkow.
Joe Garcia, played by Michael Peña.
A Working Man is a 2025 action thriller film produced and directed by David Ayer, who co-wrote the
screenplay with Sylvester Stallone, based on the 2014 novel Levon's Trade by Chuck Dixon.
It stars Jason Statham, Michael Peña and David Harbour.
In the film, soldier-turned-construction worker Levon Cade hunts down the human
traffickers who kidnapped his employer Joe Garcia's daughter Jenny.
A Working Man was released in the United States by Amazon MGM
Studios and in the United Kingdom by Warner Bros.
Pictures on March 28, 2025.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $98
million worldwide against a $40 million budget.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
kidnapping, vigilante, missing person, black ops.
The tone is intense.